<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SQL on Handbook</title><link>http://example.org/sql/</link><description>Recent content in SQL on Handbook</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 09:20:58 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/sql/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Common Expressions</title><link>http://example.org/sql/common-expressions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 14:40:19 +0800</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/sql/common-expressions/</guid><description>CASE # CASE WHEN condition1 THEN result1 WHEN condition2 THEN result2 WHEN conditionN THEN resultN ELSE result END; The CASE expression goes through conditions and returns a value when the first condition is met (like an if-then-else statement). So, once a condition is true, it will stop reading and return the result. If no conditions are true, it returns the value in the ELSE clause.If there is no ELSE part and no conditions are true, it returns NULL.</description></item><item><title>Common Functions</title><link>http://example.org/sql/common-functions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 14:24:02 +0800</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/sql/common-functions/</guid><description>COALESCE # SELECT COALESCE(NULL, NULL, NULL, &amp;#39;W3Schools.com&amp;#39;, NULL, &amp;#39;Example.com&amp;#39;); Return the first non-null value in a list. See also w3schools.
IFNULL # SELECT IFNULL(NULL, &amp;#34;W3Schools.com&amp;#34;); Return the specified value IF the expression is NULL, otherwise return the expression. See also w3schools.
IF # SELECT IF(500&amp;lt;1000, &amp;#34;YES&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;NO&amp;#34;); The IF() function returns a value if a condition is TRUE, or another value if a condition is FALSE. See also w3schools.</description></item><item><title>Views</title><link>http://example.org/sql/views/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 14:47:58 +0800</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/sql/views/</guid><description>Altering view # The CREATE OR REPLACE VIEW command updates a view. See also w3schools.
CREATE OR REPLACE VIEW [Brazil Customers] AS SELECT CustomerName, ContactName, City FROM Customers WHERE Country = &amp;#34;Brazil&amp;#34;; WITH CHECK OPTION # The WITH CHECK OPTION clause can be given for an updatable view to prevent inserts to rows for which the WHERE clause in the select_statement is not true. It also prevents updates to rows for which the WHERE clause is true but the update would cause it to be not true (in other words, it prevents visible rows from being updated to nonvisible rows).</description></item><item><title>Stored Procedures</title><link>http://example.org/sql/stored-procedures/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 15:14:52 +0800</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/sql/stored-procedures/</guid><description>Defining Stored Programs in MySQL # If you use the mysql client program to define a stored program containing semicolon characters, a problem arises. By default, mysql itself recognizes the semicolon as a statement delimiter, so you must redefine the delimiter temporarily to cause mysql to pass the entire stored program definition to the server. To redefine the mysql delimiter, use the delimiter command. See also MySQL Reference manual.</description></item></channel></rss>